Loading, please wait...

Privacy Notice - Your Privacy Rights
====================================

Effective Date: January 1, 2018

Last Updated: October 11, 2023

### About This Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice describes the information and collection practices on the websites, mobile applications, products, and services (collectively “Services”) that link to this Privacy Notice. These Services are provided by the provider companies listed on [https://www.pdffiller.com/en/contracting-entities.htm](https://www.pdffiller.com/en/contracting-entities.htm) . It does not apply to our use of employee or job applicant information.

We adhere to the principles of the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (DPF), the Swiss-U.S. DPF, and the UK extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. To learn more, click [here](#transfers_of_us).  

We may process your personal information under an agreement with a third party and act as a data processor. For example, if a business customer uploads a contract for signature we will process the information under instructions from the customer. In those cases, the terms of that agreement may also govern how your information is used. If you believe a third party has asked us to process your personal information on their behalf, please contact them first.

NOTICE OF COLLECTION  

### **Collection of Personal Information**  

The type of personal information we collect depends on your relationship with us and the Services you use. California law requires us to tell you if we share information for cross-contextual behavioral advertising. Described below by category is the information we may collect. We also indicate if we share it for cross-contextual behavioral advertising. To learn how to modify your cross-contextual advertising preferences, view our  [Notice of Right to Opt-out of Sale/Sharing](#Notice_of_Right):

* Documents. We store and process the files you upload to your account. We use the files only as you instructed us to.
* Contact information. This includes your name and email address. It also includes a mailing address, phone number, or electronic signature.
* Commercial information. This includes billing and payment information (e.g., credit card number, expiration date), products or services purchased.
* Geolocation. This includes physical location and precise location including when you sign up for or use our Services as well as when you sign an electronic document.  
    
* Submitted information. We collect any information you submit to us. This includes feedback or questions.
* Usage Information. We collect personal information about how you use our Services and the devices you use to access our Services including (i) logs and session data, (ii) browser and operating system information, (iii) which site or mobile application you came from, (iv) which site you visit when you leave us, (v) areas of our site or mobile application you visit and any actions you make, and (vi) your IP address. We also collect device identifiers. This might include your hardware model and operating system. In some cases, we may share this information for the purposes noted [below](#Use_of_PI).
* Transactional data. We may collect the names and email addresses of parties to a transaction. We may also collect the subject line and the history of an individual's actions in connection with a transaction. We may also collect personal information about those individuals or their devices. This might include name, email address, IP address, and authentication methods.

We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information, as defined by California law, for inferring characteristics or for purposes other than those permitted by law.  

### **Use of Personal Information**  

We use information for the following reasons:

* To respond to your request and communicate with you. We use information to create your account and manage your relationship with us. This includes communication about our terms and policies. We use information to respond to your questions. These may be customer service questions or questions about product education and training.  
    
* To provide and improve our Services. We use information to provide you with our Services. For example, we record details about transactions involving electronic documents. We use information to collect payments and respond to related inquiries. We use information to make our Services better and develop new features. This also includes customizing your experience with us. We may also use information to analyze how our Services are used.  
    
* To conduct marketing activities. We use information to let you know about new features and products. These might be our offers or products, or third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting. We may also let you know about special events. We may do this by phone, online, or by email. We may use information to conduct surveys or run sweepstakes or other contests.  
    
* To protect our company and constituents. We use information to protect our company and customers, and users. This includes complying with our legal obligations. We use information to identify fraud and secure our systems and Services.

We use information for other purposes as permitted by law or as we may disclose to you.

EU Lawful Basis for Processing Your Personal Information. If UK or European data protection law applies and where we act as a data controller, our lawful basis for collecting and using the personal information described here will depend on the type of personal information and the specific context in which we collect or use it. In those cases, we either use information (i) where we have your consent to do so, (ii) where we need the personal information to provide you with Services or to perform a contract with you, or (iii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. We may have a legal obligation to collect or retain personal information or may need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person. For example, when we:

* Use personal information to create and manage an account, we do so to provide you with relevant Services and perform our contract with you.  
    
* Gather and record data associated with the use of a digital certificate or electronic signature. We do so to comply with regulations.  
    
* Use names and email addresses for email marketing purposes, we do so with your consent (which you can withdraw at any time) or, where permitted under applicable law, based on our legitimate interests.  
    
* Gather usage data and analyze it to improve our Services, make conscientious adjustments to meet our growing customer base’s needs, or ensure the security of our Services, we do so based on our legitimate interest in safeguarding and improving our Services.

**Google API**. Provider’s use and transfer of information received from Google APIs to any other app adheres to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use requirements. Provider uses information received from Google APIs solely to provide or improve user-facing features that are prominent in the requesting application's user interface. Provider transfers such information only as allowed under the Limited Use Requirements and does not transfer or sell this information to third parties or to serve advertising.

More information  

We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information, as defined by California law, for inferring characteristics or for purposes other than those permitted by law. Review our  [retention practices](#Retention_of_PI) below. For more information about our privacy practices, read the rest of this Privacy Notice below.  

### **How We Collect Information**  

Information we collect directly from you. We collect information if you create an account or contact us. We also collect information when you start, sign, edit, fill in, or review an electronic document. We collect information when you participate in surveys or sign up for communications and when you engage with us on social media or community forums. This could be done in person, online, or by phone.

Information we collect automatically and passively. We collect information about users over time and across different websites and applications. We also work with third parties that collect personal information this way. We use several common tracking tools to collect information. Tracking tools include browser cookies and web beacons. To learn more about cookies, visit FTC’s Online Tracking  [here](https://consumer.ftc.gov/articles/how-protect-your-privacy-online#understanding_cookies) . We may work with others to gather information on our platforms and elsewhere. We may do this on our websites and in emails we send to you. We collect information about users over time when you use our websites. For choices you may have on what information we automatically collect, please see  [Your Choices](#Your_Choices) below.

Information we collect from others. Business partners may provide information about you to us. This includes marketers, partners, and researchers. If you register for our Services on another website, the website may provide your personal information to us. Other customers may give us your personal information. For example, a customer might send you a document to fill out and sign. When they d o, they will give us your email address and name. If a customer wants to add you to an existing account, they will send us information about you. Referral sources will share information about you to send a referral. If you use a third-party profile to set up your account with us, we will receive information associated with that third-party profile.

We Combine Information

We may combine the personal information we receive from other sources with the personal information we collect from you and use it as described here. This includes information received through LinkedIn, Apple Sign-In, Microsoft, Google OneTap, and Facebook. We also combine information we collect from you online with information we receive from you offline. We combine information that we have collected across third-party platforms. We combine information across devices.  

### **Disclosing Information to Others**  

We disclose personal information as follows:

* Service Providers. We share all categories of your information with service providers to support our Services. These include providers of smart search technology and data analytics. It also includes quality control, security and advertising providers. We may also share all categories of information with payment processing or fraud detection services. It also includes authentication systems and customer support providers.
* Affiliates. We may share all categories of information with other companies under our common ownership or control. These companies use your personal information as described in this Privacy Notice. This includes current and future companies. For a current list of our contracting entities, please visit: [https://www.pdffiller.com/en/contracting-entities.htm](https://www.pdffiller.com/en/contracting-entities.htm).
* Marketing Partners. We may share your contact information with sponsors of events, webinars, or sweepstakes for which you register or other parties with whom we may engage in joint marketing activities.
* Public or Government Authorities. We may share all categories of information to comply with our legal obligations, regulations, or contracts or to respond to a court order, administrative, or judicial processes, such as a subpoena, government audit, or search warrant where we are legally required to do so. We also may share your information when there are threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our policies or other agreements, or to protect the legal rights of third parties, including our employees, users, or the public.
* Corporate Transactions. All categories of your personal information may be disclosed or transferred to relevant third parties in the event of, or as part of the due diligence for, any proposed or actual reorganization, sale, merger, consolidation, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or part of our business, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceeding).
* Other internal users. When you allow others to access, use, or edit content in your account, we share that content with them. For example, if you send a document to others for review or signature, we make the contents of the document available to them. When you create a profile, other users may be able to view your profile information.
* Public Information. Information that you have made publicly available (your public profile or discussion forum) will be made broadly available to others. When you comment on our social media pages or in our community forums, this information may also be read, collected, and used by others. This could be used to contact you, send you unsolicited messages, or for purposes neither we nor you have control over. We are not responsible for personal or any other information you submit in these forums.
* Your Employer or Organization. When you create an account or user role with an email address assigned to you as an employee, contractor, or member of an organization (e.g., yourname@youremployer.com or yourname@nonprofit.org) or a personal email that you are authorized to use with an organization (e.g., yourname@gmail.com), that organization (if it is our customer with certain features) can find your account and take certain actions that may affect your account, including monitoring the activity, suspending, and terminating your account. If you have questions or concerns about the level of access and control your employee or organization has over your account, you should contact them for more information.
* Consent. We may share your personal information in other ways if you have asked us to do so or you have given consent. For example, you may ask us to send your personal information to a third party of your choosing.

We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you or as otherwise permitted by law.  

### **Retention of Personal Information**  

We keep your personal information for as long as necessary or relevant for the purposes for which it is processed. We also keep information as required by law. You can control and delete documents in your account at any time. If the document has been shared with another party, it will remain visible to them until either they delete it or it is deleted by all parties with access to the document.  

**Your Choices**  

You have certain choices described here. You can also decide what information you give us. If you do not provide us with certain personal information, you may not be able to use some parts of our Services. For example, if you do not adopt an electronic signature, then you will not be able to sign certain documents electronically. This section describes other choices you have:

* Profile. You are not required to fill out a profile. If you do, you can access and review this personal information. If any personal information is inaccurate or incomplete, you can make changes in your account settings. We may make changes to your account if the change is requested by you, your employer (if the account is used for business purposes), or our business customer who controls your account.
* Marketing. You can opt out of email marketing messages we send you by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in the email message or by visiting the  [Privacy Request Portal](https://arsl.at/DGvPK3AB). Please note that we may send you one message to confirm you want to opt out. We will continue to send transactional or relationship messages after you opt out of marketing messages. If you would like your phone number added to our Do-Not-Call list to opt out of telemarketing messages, please visit the  [Privacy Request Portal](https://arsl.at/DGvPK3AB).
* Cookies and Other Related Technology. You can manage cookies through your browser settings or our Cookie Preference Center and other methods detailed in our Cookie Notice ( [https://www.pdffiller.com/en/cookies.htm](https://www.pdffiller.com/en/cookies.htm)). However, if you decline cookies, you may not be able to use some parts of our Services.
* Shine the Light. California residents may ask for a list of third parties that have received their personal information for direct marketing purposes during the previous calendar year. This list also contains the types of personal information shared. We provide this list at no cost. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please contact us via the  [Privacy Request Portal](https://arsl.at/DGvPK3AB).
* Device and Usage Information. If you do not want us to see your device location, you can turn off location sharing on your device, change your device privacy settings, or decline to share the location on your browser.
* Closing Your Account. If you wish to close your account, please log in to your account and delete the account through account settings. If you need assistance closing your account, you can contact the support team through the means described on the relevant website. Please include in your email your first name, last name, company (if applicable), and a list of Services you wish to cancel. As part of our security and privacy practices, we are unable to go into your account to delete any documents or export certain documents as it would require us to have direct access to the documents in your account. If you intend to close your account with us, we encourage you to export all necessary documents before closing your account. Once an account has been closed we will deactivate your account and within a reasonable amount of time begin the process to delete the account along with any remaining documents. Once the deletion process is complete we cannot guarantee that you will be able to re-activate your account or recover documents associated with your original account.

**Children and Our Services**  

Our Services are not designed for and are not marketed to children under 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children. Users of our services may send forms or notices that gather personal information about minors. Users are responsible for obtaining appropriate consents. If you are a parent or legal guardian and believe we have your child’s information, please contact us through the  [Privacy Request Portal](https://arsl.at/DGvPK3AB). We will delete personal information that we learn is collected from a minor.  

**Your Privacy Rights**  

Under certain laws you may have additional rights related to your personal information. Those rights are described in more detail below. To exercise any of these rights, please visit the  [Privacy Request Portal](https://arsl.at/DGvPK3AB).

* You can access and review personal information associated with your account that you have provided us by logging into your account with us and reviewing the information listed in your profile.
* You can request to know the following:
* How we collect and use your personal information and why;
* The categories of personal information we have collected and the categories of recipients of your personal information;
* How we received your personal information and its source;
* Our business purpose for using your personal information; and
* How long we use or store your personal information or the manner in which we determine relevant retention periods.

* You have a right to correct inaccurate personal information about you.
* In certain situations, you can request that we erase/delete or stop using your personal information.
* In certain situations you can object to or restrict our use of your personal information.
* You have the right to ask us to export your personal information to another third party of your choosing or provide you with a  copy of your personal information.
* Where we rely on your consent to process your personal information, you can withdraw consent you may have already provided at any time. This will not affect the lawfulness of the processing prior to the withdrawal of your consent. You have the right not to be discriminated against for exercising a privacy right.
* If you are unsatisfied with our response to your complaint, you have a right to raise questions or complaints with your local data protection authority at any time.

Notice of Right to Opt-out of Sale/Sharing. California, Nevada, and Virginia law require that we tell you if we sell personal information to a third party for monetary or (in California) other valuable consideration. We do not do this. We also do not sell personal information of minors under the age of 16 for monetary or other valuable consideration. We may share information with third parties in order to provide cross-contextual behavioral advertising. This sharing provides you with more tailored and personalized content and ads. In the Notice at Collection (above), we outlined which categories of information are shared for cross-contextual behavioral advertising. Some browsers also allow you to tell websites not to share your information for cross-contextual behavioral advertising. We will respond to these signals in a frictionless manner. If you configure this setting on your browser, certain features on our site may not work and you will receive less targeted advertising. To learn how to configure this setting, view  [here](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) . Additionally, the Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising provides consumers with the ability to manage certain choices online  [here](https://optout.aboutads.info/?amp;lang=EN&lang=EN&c=2)  and provides a tool for managing mobile choices [here](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) . Selections are browser and device-specific.

How it works. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact us via the  [Privacy Request Portal](https://arsl.at/DGvPK3AB). For security purposes and as required by law, if you make a request to exercise the rights referenced above, we will require you to provide certain information for identity verification purposes. If you have an account with us, we may verify you through the login of your account. If you do not have an account with us, we may require you to provide additional information from which we can confirm your identity. Where permitted by law you may authorize an agent to make a request to us on your behalf, and we will verify the identity of your agent or authorized legal representative by either seeking confirmation from you or documents that establish the agent’s authorization to act on your behalf.

Exceptions. In some cases, we may not be able to complete your request because an exception exists under applicable law. For example, we may need to keep some information to provide the Services.  

**Transfers to the U.S. and Third Countries**  

EU-U.S. / Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework. We participate in the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (DPF), the Swiss-U.S. DPF, an the UK extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. We comply with the DPF Principles with respect to personal information transferred from the EEA, Switzerland, and UK to the United States in reliance on the DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Notice and the DPF Principles, the DPF Principles shall govern. To learn more about the DPF program, and to view our certification, please visit [www.dataprivacyframework.gov](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/). 

airSlate, Inc.’s controlled U.S. subsidiaries and affiliates, as identified in our self-certification and below, also adhere to the DPF Principles:

* AIRSLATE LEGAL FORMS, INC.
* DOCHUB LLC
* INSTAPAGE, INC.

We are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. If third-party agents process personal information on our behalf in a manner inconsistent with the DPF Principles, we remain liable unless we prove we are not responsible for the event giving rise to any damages. If you have a question or complaint related to our compliance with the DPF Principles, please contact us as indicated at the bottom of this Privacy Notice. For any complaints related to the DPF that cannot be resolved with us directly, you may refer the matter, free of charge, to JAMS Mediation, Arbitration and ADR Services, an independent dispute resolution body based in the United States, at [https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-data-privacy-framework](https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-data-privacy-framework). Finally, under limited circumstances and after other available dispute resolution mechanisms have been exhausted, binding arbitration is available to address certain residual complaints under the DPF not resolved by other means (see [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf) for details).

For other transfers to Third Countries, we have adopted the Standard Contractual Clauses to facilitate the transfer of personal information from the European Economic Area, Switzerland, and/or United Kingdom to our company and affiliates, and/or service providers outside of these countries. Transfers outside the group of our companies are only made to organizations that agree to adhere to the security and privacy standards in our Data Processing Addendum and our Standard Contractual Clauses or use another valid alternative under data protection law. You may view our Data Processing Addendum and Standard Contractual Clauses at [https://www.pdffiller.com/en/dpa.htm](https://www.pdffiller.com/en/dpa.htm) .

**Security Measures**  

We use reasonable security measures as required by relevant law. The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites or platforms will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.  

**Third-Party Sites and Links**  

If you click on a link to a third-party website, you will be taken to sites we do not control. This includes our social media pages. These third-parties’ privacy practices may be different than ours, and our Privacy Notice does not apply to their actions. We are not responsible for these third-party practices and encourage you to read their privacy notices carefully.  

**Changes to This Privacy Notice**  

We may make changes or updates to this Privacy Notice. We will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Notice as required by law. This may include posting changes on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.  

**How to Contact Us**  

For questions or complaints regarding our use of your personal information or this Privacy Notice, please contact us via [email](mailto:privacy@airslate.com) or by sending a letter to airSlate Inc. Attention: Data Privacy Officer, 17 Station Street, 3rd Floor, Brookline, Massachusetts 02445.

We use cookies to improve security, personalize the user experience, enhance our marketing activities (including cooperating with our marketing partners) and for other business use. Click [here](https://www.pdffiller.com/en/cookies.htm "Cookie Policy") to read our Cookie Policy. By clicking “Accept“ you agree to the use of cookies. ... Read moreRead less

Accept
